{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835162748","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835162748"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835162810","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835162809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d4f381f1-6379-4040-92b9-7ab96027e6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835168876","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835168876"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d4f381f1-6379-4040-92b9-7ab96027e6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835173685","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835173684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d4f381f1-6379-4040-92b9-7ab96027e6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835179269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835179269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d4f381f1-6379-4040-92b9-7ab96027e6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835337269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835337268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d4f381f1-6379-4040-92b9-7ab96027e6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835337366","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835337366"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d8a38922-83e3-4280-8486-a1d620cdac74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835343810","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835343810"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d8a38922-83e3-4280-8486-a1d620cdac74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835350710","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835350709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d8a38922-83e3-4280-8486-a1d620cdac74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.115","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835356869","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835356868"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d8a38922-83e3-4280-8486-a1d620cdac74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835572388","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835572388"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" d8a38922-83e3-4280-8486-a1d620cdac74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835572488","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835572488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835579109","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835579109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835585267","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835585267"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.115","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835590983","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835590982"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835600322","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835600322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835606829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835606829"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835613415","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835613414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.115","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835618874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835618874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835623830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835623829"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835629607","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835629606"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835634807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835634806"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.115","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835640625","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835640625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835647333","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835647332"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543835655304","data":{"timestamp":" 1543835655304"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 839fb255-ab1f-4986-b6b4-0881f3336056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853070656","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853070655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853076662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853076662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853083348","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853083348"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853089512","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853089512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-3-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853096828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853096827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853105654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853105654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-5-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853111385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853111385"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853117724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853117723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853124343","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853124343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-0-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853129888","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853129888"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853136650","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853136649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853147951","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853147951"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853157370","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853157370"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 0f19940c-378b-4022-97ff-97b406a2e4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853167562","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853167561"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853178933","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853178933"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853182381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853182380"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853186747","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853186747"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853190049","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853190049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853193256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853193256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853197216","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853197216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853201275","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853201275"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853204372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853204372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853207667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853207667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853211335","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853211334"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853215039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853215039"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853218153","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853218153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853221523","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853221523"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853225031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853225031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853228112","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853228112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853234198","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853234198"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853237682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853237682"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853241242","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853241242"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853245004","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853245004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853248205","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853248205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853251807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853251807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853255119","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853255119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853260793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853260793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853264240","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853264239"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853269425","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853269425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853273303","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853273302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" 363f558b-e602-41dd-8074-0a57e490da2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853281140","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853281140"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" cc2a94e4-a58c-41ab-bbb1-29ab82a6a920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853309175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853309175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-1-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853314596","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853314596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853555009","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853555009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853560011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853560011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853565182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853565182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853570486","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853570486"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-7-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853584249","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853584249"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_7-2-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543853590569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543853590569"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_140327"," gameId":" e6a0480d-8775-419a-97bc-d76c07380e22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}